Once there was a man who obtained everything, the legendary Pirate King Gold Roger.
His last words before he was executed inspired people to sail the seas.
All my wealth and treasure?
It can be yours if you want!
Search for it!
I left everything in that one place.
People now set sail in search of romance.
The world has entered a Great Age of Pirates!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
Now raise our flag to the Break of Romance Dawn.
Translation & initial timing
Yibis Fansubs
Let the waves crash, they'll jump start us out of sleep.
Timing
Galaxy 9000
Time-checking
Sewil
If we're going to go to an incredible world,
Quality-checking
Sewil
Galaxy 9000
you'll have to be tough.
Soundtracking
Halee
Standing out too much, is that a crime?
Wanted → Means a Winner ( • v • )
Freedom is our only rule!
Forget our worries, just let the wind blow.
I'm sure we'll be the first to find One Piece!
Video editing
Sewil
Our hearts dream beyond measure...
so let's never wake them up.
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
Dawn can't come soon enough, I'm tired of waiting!
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We... made it this far.
We'll go... wherever our dreams take us,
and we won't leave anyone behind.
We'll go at it with all our hearts, that's a vow.
On that day when our dreams began,
we set our goals and they've never changed!
I can't stay still! I can't stop!
The sun in my heart will never set!
One, two, Sunshine...
One, two, Sunshine, four... We Go!
We Go!
W-W-Wait!  Luffy-san?!
Hey!  Wait, Megalo!
Where are you going?!
Father, brothers, and everyone in the castle...
Please forgive me!
I'm going out without permission!
I'll be back in time for dinner!
Let's go for a walk!
What are you doing, Megalo?!
You left the door to Koukaku Tower wide open.
What if something happens to the princess?!
Pirate!  Hurry and see to the princess's safety!
You're working my bones too hard.
She's gone!  Princess Shirahoshi is gone!
What?!  The Mermaid Princess is not here?!
This is awful!  A national crisis!
When did this happen?  Who could have done this?!
She's been kidnapped!
Kidnapped?!
Princess!
Oh, princess.
She's been kidnapped, has she-
Hey!  What are you doing?!
The channel that connects
Ryuuguu Palace and Fishman Island...
Where is the switch to open it?!
What?  Switch?
Either way, we must hurry back to Neptune-sama, Skeleton!
We need to report this to him immediately!
We've got no choice.
Following their orders is our only chance of survival.
Tell us already!
Who are "they"?
If you don't, they'll kill us!
Kill you?!
What are you talking about?!
Listen up, pirates working for Hody Jones!
You're in luck!
You get to be a part of this historic event!
Vander Decken...
Isn't he the captain of the Flying Dutchman?
The captain of the cursed ghost ship?
Don't worry, I'm just his descendant.
I'm not a ghost.
But I, too, have been cursed.
I'm a fishman, yet I can't swim.
Let me show you the power of the devil
that I gained with the Mato Mato curse!
Alright, you'll do.  Human, come forth.
Hody!
Are you really going to do this?!
Stop this madness!
It's him!  Hachi-san!
It's Hachi-san!
It's Hacchan-san!
Hachi-san.
The Energy Steroid is just a drug that destroys your body!
Why are fishmen trying to destroy Fishman Island?!
Don't underestimate
the champion of the sea, Neptune!
Hachi-san, give it a rest.
I have no interest in your opinion.
I can hardly believe that
you were once a member of the crew I looked up to.
You've become weak.
Your time has passed.
I need Fishman Island if I want to teach
the humans a lesson, and Neptune is in my way.
You guys were the ones who taught us
that we are the superior species.
But Arlong-san lost!
Decken!  Hyouzou!  Why are you siding with him?!
You refused Arlong-san's invitation back then,
so why are you helping these young fools now?!
Helping?  I'm just working here because he pays me.
Arlong didn't want to part with his cash
so he couldn't employ me.
Too bad Arlong could only obtain a swordsman of your caliber.
So you're Hachi from Arlong's crew, huh?
Now that sure takes me back!
Your captain once tried to recruit me as his underling.
But I couldn't agree to that.
I could never let someone boss me around.
Hody here understands that.
Arlong-san's ambition and his
ability to act on it were admirable.
However, he was all brawn and no brains.
Even if we wanted to, we were too young to become pirates while you were out raising a ruckus at sea.
And now everyone who grew up in those days
has assembled here.
So our resolve is strong, and we've learned from our predecessors' mistakes.
I am the man who will carry on Arlong's will.
And you, a former member of the crew I admired, are saying that you have a problem with my plan?
That's really discouraging, Hachi-san!
And while we're on the subject, Straw Hat Luffy is here.  The very man who shattered your ambitions.
Don't you even care about that?!
He called me his friend,
even though I used to be a member of Arlong's crew!
The three of you are my friends!
I owe Straw Hat Luffy my life!
I would go to meet him right now...
but while Arlong's will lives on,
I couldn't possibly face him!
Humans are your friends?!  You piece of trash!
I'm utterly disappointed in you!
I'm locked on to you, Hachi.
Have you forgotten how pirates do things?
If you have a problem with someone,
you'll have to resolve it with violence...
I presume!
Where'd he throw it?
When I touched you just now, you became my target.
Whatever I throw and wherever I throw it...
it will change its course like a hunting bird,
and head straight for its target: You!
It looked like he threw that knife in some random direction, and...
It hit the octopus fishman!
The Mato Mato curse...
Of course, there are several ways to stop it.
Why don't we give it a try?
Stop!  Don't throw all those arrows.
I've heard rumors about your ability.
Hey, Hody, he'll kill me at this rate!
Please, stop Decken!
Didn't he just tell you, Hachi-san?
Vander Decken is not my underling.
We're two pirates who have made an alliance on equal terms.
Besides, you're just a nuisance.
You damn coward!
Damn it!
Here we go!
Good!  Run away, run away!
But wherever you go...
Wherever you go...
Wherever you go... they'll chase you down!
If only I could make it outside.
Alright, now I can escape!
Those arrows won't be able to follow me in the water.
Damn!  So it doesn't matter
if they're in the water or not?!
Stay away!
The number of targets I can keep in my memory is the same as my number of hands.
Two of them.
My right hand, that I haven't washed for ten years,
stores the memory of when I touched
the princess of Ryuuguu Palace.  Shirahoshi herself!
You get it?!  All the love and weapons I throw...
will pursue my target even into the depths of Hell!
That is my power!
Amazing!
So that's how you've been able to keep up
your insidious stalker crush...
without being seen or caught by the Neptune Army!
Indeed!
What a cunning man!
Cunning!  Cunning!
Now then, human pirates.
You understand Decken's ability now, right?
So now it's time to begin phase one of our plan.
They say it's impossible to
break into Ryuuguu Palace...
but one man has been able to
throw things in there for the last ten years.
Namely, Vander Decken.
In other words, this plan consist of you being the objects thrown by Decken...
and flying straight toward the Mermaid Princess in Ryuuguu Palace.
Though, you'll actually crash into the tower's hard walls.
Then, once you're inside Ryuuguu Palace, you'll open the gates from the inside,
and let us in.  That is your mission.
No way!  If you do that...
We'll crash into the walls and die!
Indeed you will.
Which is why we're using the lives of you worthless humans!
Down here, you're worth less than slaves!
Those who survive the crash will carry out the mission!
If it goes well, I will set you free.
If you refuse the mission, then...
I will throw you outside the bubble right now,
you inferior species!
N-No way!  If you do that, we'll drown!
In that case, you just have to take your chances on the method that leaves some slight chance of survival!
Go!
Today,
is the beginning of a new chapter in history for us fishmen!
It starts when we conquer the Ryuuguu Kingdom!
Yeah!
I'm coming now, Shirahoshi!
And now we return to the present.
Wait!
I will not wait!
Hurry, skeleton!  To the king!
Wait!  We have to open the way...
Or Hody will kill us!
Hey, Sanji!
He ended up...
beating up all the soldiers.
We hadn't done anything wrong!
Well, they wanted to put me in handcuffs!
Look!  Everyone is looking at us so coldly!
Their eyes are like the fish of the deep sea!
Oh, quit whining.  It's too late now.
You should have thought about that
before beating them up!
You took out half of them too!  With your Kung Fu!
You were pretty strong.
E-Even if you say that, I'm not happy at all, you jerk!
The voice of a lady!
Someone covered in blood has washed ashore!
Aren't you from the Fishman District?!
What happened?!
Someone, get a doctor!
I'm a doctor!
Hachi?!
What happened to you?!
Hey, Hachi, it's us!
How did you get all those injuries?!
What happened?!
It's you guys.
I'm glad I found you.  Is Straw Hat here?
He's not.  Wait, I'll help you.
Gather your crew.  Hurry!
You're better off...
not getting involved in this island's affairs any more.
Leave Fishman Island.
The New Fishman Pirates are going to
attack this island!
Ryuuguu Kingdom will be destroyed!
Neptune-sama!
She's been kidnapped!
The princess was carried off by someone or another!
Also, a group of pirates came raining down by the tower.
Anyway, we are under attack!  Under attack!
Kidnapped?!  Who could have taken Shirahoshi?!
An enemy attack, now?
What are we going to do?
Why now?!
We're already attacking the palace ourselves!
W-What should we do?!
On second thought, don't answer that!
We'll cut them down.
I said don't answer!
If we're going to survive...
We have to open the gate to the palace!
H-Here they come!
Aren't you gonna come out of the shark now?
N-No, I'd rather stay inside.
How does it feel,
being outside for the first time in ten years?
My heart won't stop racing.
I have done something really awful.
Just going outside isn't bad!
You're so weird.
Is this...
what they call an "adventure"?
Yeah.
If you're this excited, then it's an adventure alright!
You said something about the Sea Forest, right?
What is that?  Is it a fun place?
A grave...
There's a grave there that I haven't visited once since it was built.
Not once in all these ten years.
It's the one place I've wanted to go to the most!
Has it really been ten years...
since the assassination that took place in broad daylight, throwing Fishman Island into chaos?
How time flies.
The princes have grown into fine warriors...
and Princess Shirahoshi is still inside that tower.
But nobody has forgotten about your ideals,
Queen Otohime.